

+375 29 586-30-56

@BykStanislav

bykstanislav@gmail.com

# Stanislav Byk

## data analyst



#### About myself

Data Analyst and Bachelor of Economics (Belarusian State Economic University).

I possess skills in data management: cleaning, structuring, metric analysis, and visualization. I am especially passionate about working with Python and confidently use SQL for database management and Git for version control. I have experience conducting A/B tests and identifying growth opportunities for businesses.

I aim to develop in the field of data analytics, applying analytical skills and economic knowledge to solve business challenges.



:::::

#### Certificates, courses

@https://github.com/Byk-Stanislav

Data Analyst Year: 2024

Organizer: KARPOV.COURSES



#### Education

Belarus State Economic University

Faculty: Economics and

management

Specialty: Economics and management at the enterprise

Degree: Bachelor

Year of graduation: 2021 Form of education: Full-time



#### Work experience

From July 2024

Project work: A/B testing, functions for data cleaning and calculating. business metrics.

July 2023 - June 2024

Herbermontage GmbH & Co: solar panel installer.

December 2022 - June 2023

Triovist: delivery point administrator

- economist (planning and economic department)
- sales manager

July 2021 - November 2021

Lohoysk municipal services: economist (planning

and economic department)
March 2021 - June 2022
CDEK: sales manager



### Key Skills

- English language (B2)
- Russian language (C2)
- Python
- Pandas
- NumPy
- SciPY
- Matplotlib
- Seaborn)

- SOL
- ClickHouse
- Tabix
- Git
- Gitlab
- Github)
- Data visualization
- Tableau

- Airflow
- A/B tests
- Data cleaning and preparation
- Statistical analysis
- Statistical metrics
- Statistical analysis of data
- Data ethics